{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/3971","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3971","name":"Hood Kafe","address":"15349 McNichols W.","zipcode":"48235","owner":"Kenneth K. Johnson","licenseNumber":"221005","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.19775,42.41578","geojson":{"id":"3971","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.197746649,42.415779509]},"properties":{"name":"Hood Kafe","owner":"Kenneth K. Johnson","address":"15349 McNichols W.","zipcode":"48235","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"221005","establishmentid":"3971","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2018-05-10"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51623157","name":"Taste Buds","address":"15349 W. McNichols","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"3818","name":"Belie's Pizza and Deli","address":"15349 McNichols Rd. W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4044","name":"Oriental Meat Market","address":"15349 McNichols Rd. W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2379","name":"Volcano Wok","address":"15315 McNichols Ave. W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"51622567","name":"Beauty Cafe dba Detroit Waffle Cafe","address":"15300 McNichols W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"51622706","name":"The Beauty Cafe","address":"15300 McNichols W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2026","name":"Palushaj's Olympia Coney Island","address":"15425 McNichols Rd. W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"961","name":"Archer's Cocktail Lounge","address":"15145 McNichols Ave. W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1413","name":"Lady Louisa's Place","address":"15535 McNichols Rd. W.","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"51622870","name":"Wild Wild West Wings","address":"15535  McNichols W.","zipcode":"48235"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45757","inspectionDate":"2019-03-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-102.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall demonstrate this knowledge by compliance with this Code, by being a certified FOOD protection manager who has shown proficiency of required information through passing a test that is part of an ACCREDITED PROGRAM, or by responding correctly to the inspector's questions as they relate to the specific FOOD operation. (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Does not demonstrate required knowledge","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"Throughout Facility","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Facility","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"Throughout Facility","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.12","violationDescription":"Frozen POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) that is slacked to moderate the temperature shall be held:    \n(A) Under refrigeration that maintains the FOOD temperature at 5°C (41°F) or less; or  \n(B) At any temperature if the FOOD remains frozen.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for slacking","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"At room temperature","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"In the Sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.14","violationDescription":"During preparation, unPACKAGED FOOD shall be protected from environmental sources of contamination.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Unpackaged food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"In the Sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-04-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43617","inspectionDate":"2018-09-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING CABINET","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"That is above 70 degrees f","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use cool, running water with enough flow to remove particles."}]},{"inspectionid":"39845","inspectionDate":"2018-02-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-02-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-02-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3971"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}